Those who ceaselessly hone the art
of killing are known as masters.
These lethal abilities, dutifully
passed down through many generations,
have become what are
called modified bloodlines.
This is the story of one such master,
Hikaru Gero of the Poison Clan, and his
greatest challenge yet, to get married.
I hear you.
Oh no, I slipped through my alarm!
What's the big deal, Mom?
I said to make sure I didn't oversleep.
Now I'm going to be late for school.
I'll see ya.
If you're that eager to go to
school on your day off, be my guest.
Oh, that's right.
This is what they refer
to as a family meal.
Just one example of human behavior.
Next up, we have the
mixed-gender friendship exhibit.
In addition to the art of killing,
The Gero family taught
me about the lives of the
humans I would eventually
have to assassinate.
They lived on the other side of one-way
mirrors, unaware of what was happening.
We call it the Human Zoo.
These creatures, so fragile and
ignorant, live at the mercy of fate.
As heir to the Poison Clan, you'll be the
one responsible for sealing that fate.
Get a kiss.
My life's destiny.
The secret of the secret.
I know you want it.
I should love it.
I should love it?
Run, run, run!
What's that run?
Fun, fun, fun! You suck! No, but, but.
For a disruptive!
Little.
Thin.
Terminus.
False!
My. Ras.
Mon.
Muscle. Pleading.
Toxic! Audience. Puisquade.
Toxic!
Vert.
What do you want?
Toxic
I'm always here.
I'm strange enough.
I'm here.
What do you want?
Kill or kiss?
Let's go!
Kill or kiss.
Plus, Hell's Lashes!
My skin gives me the unique ability
to bend any fluid to my will.
Let me demonstrate!
No!
Oops, did I accidentally
hit an innocent bystander?
I'll compensate you, of course.
Well, I would if you
were going to survive.
Pei, are you going to be alright?
I'm confused.
Why go this far for me?
Because it's our job.
But in Kero's eyes, you're
more than just a client.
But what does that mean?
Just run. Leave us.
We only have one priority.
Ensuring your safe escape.
But Kero and I need a little more time.
We'll be fine.
Come on, tell me how I
can help you out already.
I lost my supply of needles and
poisons after that hit. Crap.
All that flailing is making it
impossible to get close to her.
Master Hikaru,
you must never allow yourself to engage
a master for less than five billion yen.
Only agree if victory is
absolutely guaranteed.
A master must not risk exposing his arts,
what we call modified
bloodline increments.
Also, if someone learns your secrets,
then you must kill them
without any hesitation.
Their death will both preserve the
Poison Master's legacy and build upon it.
Shut up!
Special delivery for you.
You, uh, what? For why?
Because the Water Master would have
knocked it out of the air if I'd thrown it.
So I dove in to make
sure it made the journey.
I'm rescuing you!
You should have used the opportunity
and left when you had the chance!
Your name's Gero, right?
I'll break this down for you.
You think you stormed in here,
knight and shining armor?
Well, guess again.
In case you couldn't tell, I'm
not exactly princess material.
In short, I'm the one who's rescuing you.
After all that, you leap into danger?
No idea what's going through your head.
He shouldn't have bothered
with shielding you.
No doubt you're a definite shoe-in for
this year's least worth saving award.
So tell me,
how does it feel risking your life for an
idiot and dying for absolutely nothing?
Kinosaki.
Thanks for setting me up with her.
And not someone else.
I'm glad it was Himekawa,
and she was my first.
Drop that syringe or the girl gets it.
It's empty?
Wait, I didn't see.
How'd he sneak up behind me?
I can't control the water.
You're right.
You really are a professional.
I'll call you the next
time my sink's clogged.
I've made a horrible mistake.
Is my hand in a no-touch zone?
Not like it was intentional.
I basically had no choice, and it's the
back of my hand, so I don't think it counts.
Kurosaki!
What do I do?
That rash.
You're allergic to clean air, right?
That's why your suit's filled with water.
To keep you from being exposed.
I read about it in the
Poison Master's library.
I made a cream to alleviate the symptoms.
Apply as needed.
Huh?
And why would you do that?
Because you pity me? As if.
I'm hammering the final
nail in your coffin.
I beat you.
Now I'm curing you.
That'll teach you to
never mess with me again.
It's not profitable.
Losing, I mean.
I'm sorry. Forgive me.
I swear, I'll never, ever be bad again.
I would hope not.
You know, your legitimate exhibits
are pretty baller, so focus on those.
Or will be back.
So weak.
Nothing but an amateur.
You're letting him off with a
warning instead of finishing the job?
A master kills and leaves no loose ends.
There are no exceptions.
If he dares to cross me again, then
he'll get my Thousand Torments toxin.
Letting him go may seem wishy-washy
to you, but I don't kill for free.
Is that okay with you, Himekawa?
Sure.
I'm never letting my guard down again.
You need a ride?
I can't believe you didn't get it when
I introduced my shark butt, Chomsky.
I mean, come on.
Obviously he's a shark who's my butt.
Isn't that right, Chomsky?
Welcome home, Mommy! We missed you!
Critics didn't think much
of Egg while he was alive!
He let go of most of his
works! All of them! That is...
Hey, why are you hiding in the corner?
No reason not to.
My late wife tragically passed away in a
traffic accident shortly
after we had Akiha.
Of course,
we could sell the painting
and live a carefree
life in a nice house off
the proceeds we'd make.
But instead...
We'd rather keep our family together.
Hey, Gero, get over here.
Akiha wants to say thank you. I'm good.
No need to bother.
Cut out the lone wolf act.
There's nothing wrong
with being appreciated.
Besides, humility just comes off as rude.
Hiya, mister.
I just wanted to say thank
you for rescuing my mom.
Gero,
when I heard you were a poison master,
I figured you'd be a real piece of work.
But I guess you're an
exception to the rule.
My thoughts exactly.
I was waiting for the right
time to thank you, but...
My brother, Okto?
He got that operation you helped pay for.
He's still recovering, but he's got the
energy to send me dumb selfies every day.
Can you believe it?
I tell him he's supposed to be
resting like he listens to me.
Because you're willing
to risk your life for us?
That family?
He may call his gang?
And even my little brother,
they're all able to smile again.
You do realize what you've
done is truly wonderful, right?
Hey, where do you think you're going?
The bathroom.
To do some cleaning.
For real?
Before you go, we never
discussed your reward.
Honestly, there aren't enough organs
between us to pay for the work you put in.
I'd obviously love to
offer you some money,
but we're also kind of strapped for cash
I'll give you anything
else you want though.
Just name it
Where the hell is Kinosaki
picking out what to wear again?
How long does that take?
In that case Himekawa come over and celebrate
with us three hotties out on the town.
Something wrong?
It's just the two of us.
I had no clue what I
was getting myself into.
Shark! Shark! Shark!
My turn?
Shark!
Welcome to the Belly of the Beast!
Commencing Operation Date!
Thanks to Operation White Knight,
Gato saved Himekawa from her captors.
With his likability at an all-time high,
he managed to wrangle a date with her.
Now tell her how you
feel and seal the deal!
He...
he spotted me already!
I shouldn't have expected any
less from a master assassin!
Remember, Gato.
Rule number one, subsection three
of the Kinosaki School of Dating.
If you don't know what to talk about,
complimenting something cute she's
wearing will work every time.
It shows you have an interest in her.
We're in luck.
She's covered in stuff you can bring up.
Pretty earrings, a lovely necklace,
her cute nails, or that stylish jacket.
So, that necklace of yours. Go for it!
It looks kind of old.
Is it an heirloom?
Even Himekawa's speechless.
Uh, it came with a flea
market dehumidifier.
Who could have seen that coming?
That's a perfect combo starter!
A flea market dehumidifier
that came with their jewelry!
There's tons of follow-ups for that!
Anyway, did you cut your bangs?
Don't give up yet!
And look at him and Kawa,
not me! Gero, listen.
Uh-oh, all that hard work
winning her over down the drain!
If you're not going to
eat that, then give me it.
Thanks a lot.
It's a good thing Himekawa's so easygoing!
I love these.
Did you say love? Red alert!
This is a disaster.
No choice, I've got to lend a hand!
Or the state is thin.
That must be a Greenland shark.
Wow, you know so much.
Oh wow, it's that support shark app.
That they shut down due
to horrible user reviews.
Wow, you know so much.
It even makes whale puns! Excuse me, miss.
That monitor.
It's off-limits for...
Even me?
What's the harm?
I couldn't help but notice
you barely touched your food.
What's up?
Well, actually...
The truth is...
I can't eat anything
someone else has made.
It's become second nature.
As far back as I'm able to remember,
I've done nothing but train
to become a poison master.
As far as food's concerned, all that
matters is whether it's poisoned or not.
I've always prepared my own
meals and ate them alone.
Sir, please!
Show some restraint! No.
I went through something similar.
The entire time I was
growing up, I was also alone.
I'm an orphan.
I didn't have any family, and
making friends wasn't easy for me.
And one day, a rich guy nearing
the end of his life adopted me.
Truth be told, I think he would
have been happy with anyone.
As the end was approaching,
he realized he hadn't left a legacy
behind, and it terrified him.
I inherited the Himekawa name,
not to mention a huge fortune.
A life of luxury awaited me.
That was...
Until I saw the room covered floor
to ceiling with crying portraits.
I did some digging and found out
he'd gotten them illegitimately.
They were alone like me,
completely out of place.
And so, I returned them home.
By the time the gallery was empty,
the Himekawa fortune had been
eaten up from all my expenses.
These days, I work part-time five
days a week to make ends meet.
I've got to admit, it's
kind of ridiculous.
Hardly.
You know,
that job, it was the first time
someone's ever genuinely thanked me,
and it's all because of the work you do.
You're so dedicated. I...
I've never met anyone like you.
Sorry.
Was it something I said?
Yeah, kinda.
Nobody's sung my praises like that before.
It's sort of embarrassing.
Don't say it.
Shark! Shark!
There's something I want to ask.
You and me, how would you
feel about being friends?
What are you thinking? Get out!
This was your big chance!
You had me going there.
Just friends? Sure thing.
I thought you were going to ask me out.
Honestly, I'd like to.
Only, to be very blunt, I don't
know the first thing about you.
Similarly, you don't know
the first thing about me.
While I might have made a
good impression earlier,
that's just how I seem on the surface.
Deep down, there are parts
of me that are so rotten.
I want to look away.
I want us to share more
experiences together first,
so little by little you can
get to know the real me.
And then, if you still think
I'd be a good match for you,
then I'll make that proposal.
Since that would be the first step in
finding the happy marriage I'm looking for!
So that's what you meant.
I get it.
You want this to start
off as a friendship.
You realize you just spilled
the beans on your whole plan.
What I meant to say
was... I'm in. Be warned.
I'm a thief.
Stealing my heart won't be easy.
Anyway, I figured you and
Kinosaki were a thing.
Kinosaki is my marriage
advisor. Is that all?
Miss Himekawa!
Since you can't eat
food other people make,
next time, how about
you handle our lunches?
Heads up, I'm big on rolled omelets.
Good news, Ghetto.
You're a bodyguard now for this cutie.
She's the only daughter of a big-time CEO.
I couldn't dare!
That would be cheating!
You want me to be human scum?
Don't be dramatic.
You just made a friend.
And when it comes to women, Himekawa's
the only one you really know.
There's a great big sea out
there full of millions of fish!
Kinds you've never heard of!
Getting to know a lot of
girls will help you see their
good points clearly and
learn to like them even more.
Maybe Himekawa really is the one for you.
Or maybe it's someone
you haven't even met yet.
But whoever they turn out to be, I want
you to have the best marriage possible.
Make it all
Ah
be creepy oh make a noise I'll be
I want
to
improve myself!
Who can cook attracts triple the ladies!
Daigo Oshima, economics
major. My lucky stars.
Next time, the Sound Master.